Josh Stubbs



josh.stubbs@protonmail.com



07862 320170



linkedin.com/in/kernelpanicj0sh

Summary

I have over 6 years experience within the IT industry, starting as an IT apprentice before working with several outsource companies in providing end user support for 100's of clients nationwide. I have great experience with Active Directory, Group Policy, Microsoft Exchange including cloud solutions such as Office 365, Nextcloud, Microsoft Azure and Amazon AWS.

I have a great understanding of TCP/IP and the ISO model and packet sampling/logging using Wireshark & Nmap to monitor network performance and troubleshoot issues including but not limited to packet loss, broadcast storms/ loopbacks etc.

I have excellent experience in windows server 2003 - 2019 and knowledge on RAID solutions, SAN Infrastructures, Hyper-V and VMware. I also have a great understanding on DNS, VPN and RDS. My main strengths are being an excellent communicator both in person and on the phone, I am very easy to talk to and can adapt quickly to my work environment. I am professional throughout and will provide the best customer service possible to ensure the end user is satisfied and that I have met and even exceeded there expectations, I am used to working in fast paced environments and dealing with critical situations such as major service outages.

I am very capable of using any helpdesk system provided and can easily train myself to use it to the highest efficiency, I leave detailed and technical notes for other engineers to make good use of without having to work out the issue again by themselves which would only cost more valuable time - I also make sure to keep the customer updated with the progress we are making, I like to do this by phone where possible to give them peace of mind that the issue is still being looked into and that we are working as best as we can to get the issue fixed.

Experience



Quickfix IT Analyst

Aspire Technology Solutions

Oct 2019 - Nov 2020 (1 year 2 months)

Working for a successful managed service provider providing remote and on-site IT Support, Broadband, Cloud Services and Infrastructure support for customers nationwide. My day to day roles included supporting windows 7 & 10 operating systems and general troubleshooting as well as server administration and user account management.

I was responsible for working on the help desk to a high standard and escalating any tickets that could not be resolved on first point of contact to ensure SLA's were achieved.

IT Support Analyst

technocopy

Sep 2017 - Oct 2019 (2 years 2 months)

Working with a small IT Support and printer solution provider supporting windows 7 & 10 users, managing and maintaining networks for SMB's within the north east. My day to day role included troubleshooting end user problems, managing anti-virus software and other infosec duties as well as troubleshooting server issues and maintaining critical data backups.



Atos IT Support Analyst

Atos

Oct 2016 - Sep 2017 (1 year)

I have worked with Atos as 1st line support providing outsources IT support, this included working on tickets on the help desk and resolving IT issues remotely. This provided me with more exposure to windows server including active directory, DNS, DHCP as well as using RSA technology for authentication.



IT Support Apprentice

Jul 2014 - Aug 2016 (2 years 2 months)

I worked with Baltic Training as an IT apprentice providing in-house IT support, this included troubleshooting network issues, VoIP maintenance and troubleshooting as well as general end user support. I also gained experience with managed network switches, Draytek routers and firewalls as well as network patching and cable routing.

Education



Carmel RC College

2007 - 2012

Licenses & Certifications



City & Guilds Level 3 IT Professional - City & Guilds

Skills

IT Hardware Support • IT Outsourcing • Information Technology • Customer Service • Remote User Support • Windows Server